A different breed of romantic comedy.
Merv is a comedy, romance film directed by Jessica Swale.
When their beloved dog Merv loses his spark after their split, Anna and Russ are
forced into the world's most awkward co-parenting arrangement.
Hoping to shake Merv out of his funk, Russ takes him to Florida for a
much-needed getaway-only for Anna to show up unexpectedly.
As Merv slowly gets his groove back, turns out fixing their dog's
broken heart may lead to a few sparks of their own.
Anna Finch, played by Zooey Deschanel.
Russ Owens, played by Charlie Cox.
Merv, played by Gus.
Jocelyn Bentley, played by Ellyn Jameson.
MJ Owens, played by Patricia Heaton.
Jack Owens, played by David Hunt.
Merv is a 2025 American romantic comedy film directed by Jessica
Swale and written by Dane Clark and Linsey Stewart.
It stars Charlie Cox and Zooey Deschanel.
The film explores themes of depression, florida,
boston, massachusetts, romcom, teacher.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.